{
  "strings": [
    {
      "problem": "String word = \"A few good men\";\nWhat is word.length()?",
      "answer1": "14",
      "answer2": "13",
      "answer3": "15",
      "answer4": "16",
      "correct": "14"

    },
    {
      "problem": "String word = \"A few good men\";\nWhat is word.charAt(7) ?",
      "answer1": "o",
      "answer2": "7",
      "answer3": "g",
      "answer4": "good men",
      "correct": "o"
    },
    {
      "problem": "String word = \"A few good men\";\nWhat is word.indexOf(“f”)?",
      "answer1": "0",
      "answer2": "2",
      "answer3": "1",
      "answer4": "-1",
      "correct": "2"
    },
    {
      "problem": "String word = \"A few good men\";\nWhat is word.substring(3, 7) ?",
      "answer1": "ew g",
      "answer2": "ew go",
      "answer3": "few",
      "answer4": "few[space]",
      "correct": "ew g"
    },
    {
      "problem": "Which of the following is NOT a primitive data type?",
      "answer1": "double",
      "answer2": "float",
      "answer3": "boolean",
      "answer4": "String",
      "correct": "String"
    },
    {
      "problem": "What would be output by the following program segment?\nString n1 = \"Samuel\";\nString n2 = \"Samantha\";\nSystem.out.print(n1.compareTo(n2);",
      "answer1": "false",
      "answer2": "true",
      "answer3": "a negative number, -20",
      "answer4": "a positive number, 20",
      "correct": "a positive number, 20"
    },
    {
      "problem": "String firstName = \"John \";\nString lastName = \"Doe\";\nSystem.out.println(firstName.concat(lastName));\nGuess the output.",
      "answer1": "John.concat(Doe)",
      "answer2": "JohnDoe",
      "answer3": "\"John Doe\"",
      "answer4": "JOHN DOE",
      "correct": "John Doe"
    },
    {
      "problem": "String x = \"10\";\nString y = \"20\";\nString z = x + y;\nGuess the output.",
      "answer1": "1020",
      "answer2": "30",
      "answer3": "10 20",
      "answer4": "\"10 20\"",
      "correct": "1020"
    },
    {
      "problem": "String txt = \"Hello World\";\nSystem.out.println(txt.toUpperCase());\nChoose the correct output.",
      "answer1": "Hello World",
      "answer2": "HELLO WORLD",
      "answer3": "\"Hello world\"",
      "answer4": "\"HELLO WORLD\"",
      "correct": "HELLO WORLD"
    },
    {
      "problem": "Which of these class is superclass of String and StringBuffer class?",
      "answer1": "java.util",
      "answer2": "java.lang",
      "answer3": "ArrayList",
      "answer4": "None of the above",
      "correct": "java.lang"
    }
  ]
}